-= NORM TEAM =-
-=本资源仅供学习测试,严禁用于商业途径=-
■
更多精彩 尽在 WWW.NORMTEAM.COM
字幕修改、特效：真金白人
Subtitles By：Jazzzheng
片名：地下特警/截杀威龙
我想他在里面 我要去查查看
I think he's inside. I'm gonna check it out.
伯克 等后援！
Burke, wait for backup.
他杀了我的搭档
He killed my partner.
我不等！
I'm not waiting.
听着，伯克，这是洛杉矶 不是加拿大
Listen, Burke, this is L.A., not Canada.
我们这里有程序的，你不能一个人处理此事
We have procedures here. You can't handle this alone.
有什么问题？
What's the problem?
老兄, 你在这里干什么？
Hey, man, what you doing here?
我在忙，滚吧
I'm busy. Scram.
我要教你点礼貌
I'm gonna teach you a lesson in manners.
我会修理你的 我会回来的
I'm gonna get you, man!
如同我说的 我要进去了
Like I said, I'm going in.
伯克！
Burke,Burke.
长眠的时候到了
Time to go to sleep...
去会合你的老搭挡吧
and join your old partner.
我是沙人  你阻止不了我的
I'm the Sandman. You can't stop me.
你被捕了
You're under arrest.
16个月之后
伯克刑警！请坐
Detective Burke. Have a seat.
汤姆逢格，总检察官
Tom Vogler, attorney general.
我右手边的是班金恩  在你左手边的是山母华登
On my right is Ben Keane, on your left is Sam Waldon.
我代表州长 负责狱中霹雳小组
I represent the governor. I'm heading his task force on prisons.
我和矫正委员会一起的
I'm with State Board of Corrections.
你是谁？  阿曼达贝克特
- And who are you? - Amanda Beckett.
她为我工作  伯克刑警
- She works for me. - Detective Burke.
专长: 卧底  加拿大骑警
Specialized in undercover work with the Royal Canadian Mounted Police...
派驻魁北克
stationed in Quebec.
你跟踪沙人克里斯奈勒来洛杉矶
You followed Christian Naylor, "the Sandman," to L.A.
我们的一座监狱有问题  哈瑞森监狱
We've had some problems in one of our prisons... Harrison Penitentiary.
这是本地报导 小镇新闻
It's a local piece, small-town news.
助理典狱长被谋杀
The assistant warden was murdered.
现在一名警卫暗地通知
Now a guard's intimated...
可能与一些犯人的死有关连
that it might be linked to the deaths of some prisoners...
在过去几个月之中有九名
nine in the last few months.
我们今年秋天要举行州长选举
We've got a gubernatorial election coming up this fall.
监狱己经是政见争执之处  我们不想这件事成为它的一部份
Prisons are already an issue. We don't want this to become a part of it.
州长要我负责改正这件小灾难
The governor's put me in charge of rectifying this little mishap.
我们想将你以犯人名义送去哈瑞森卧底
We wanna send you undercover into Harrison as a prisoner.
你来自魁北克  牢里没有人会认得你
You're from Quebec. No one in jail will recognize you.
只有这委员会知道你是名警员
Only this committee will know you're an officer.
你会以武装抢劫判刑去哈瑞森
You'll be sentenced to Harrison for armed robbery.
在犯人中武装劫是受尊重的罪
Armed robbery is a respectable crime among inmates.
它是绝对的暴力
It's implicitly violent.
他们尊重暴力
They respect violence.
我们同时也派一位类似搭档的人
We're also assigning a partner of sorts.
阿曼达会担任你的连络人
Amanda will act as your liaison.
她会扮演你太太  阿曼达会传递消息
She'll be posing as your wife. Amanda will relay information.
经由她 我们能监视整个行动
Through her, we'll be able to closely monitor the operation.
如何？ 刑警  你怎么说？
Well, Detective, what do you say?
我会让你们知道
I'll let you know.
你要我明早第一件事就是为你将报纸存档吗？
Would like me to file the papers for you first thing in the morning?
我想愈快愈好  我晓得你们办事一向办的很好
I think the sooner, the better. I know you always do a good job.
那么我们明晚见？  好
- We'll see you tomorrow night then? - Yeah.
若海伦要我带什么东西叫她打电话绐我
Have Helen call me if she wants me to bring anything.
我会的  再见
- I will. - Bye.
幸会 伯克先生
A pleasure meeting you, Mr. Burke.
你认识他多久了 ？  很久了
- How long have you known him? - A long time.
他一直像我的父执辈
He's really been like a father to me.
我自法学院毕业后就一直跟着他
I've been working for him ever since I graduated law school.
那是什么时候？
When was that?
去年
Last year.
有问题吗？伯克刑警
Is there a problem, Detective Burke?
你没足够的经验加入这案子
You don't have enough experience to be on this case.
我们在这把话说清楚 刑警
Let's get something straight here.
我不是玩伴女郎
I'm no girl Friday.
我在班上以第一名毕业
I graduated top in my class at Stanford.
若你对我是女人这事实不舒服
If you're uncomfortable with the fact that I'm a woman...
那是你的问题不是我的
then that's your problem, not mine.
好
Okay.
查查在哈瑞森监狱中每一个连续犯杀人案的档案
Check the files of any serial killers at Harrison Prison.
然后你就接本案？
Then you'll take the case?
我们星期二见
I'll see you Tuesday.
我去做事
I'll get to work.
路易斯
Louis.
你在淋雨
You're getting wet.
听着！
Listen up!
双手交叉放在前面
Clasp your fingers in front of you.
而且别动
And don't move.
我是迪葛夫警佐
I am Sergeant DeGraf.
我决定你们何时吃
I decide when you eat...
淋浴
when you shower...
及何时有访客
when you have visitors.
你们是菜鸟
You are fish.
新来的
New arrivals.
别人会试着伤害你们
People will try to hurt you...
抢劫你
rob you...
甚至强奸你
even rape you.
他说了别动
He said, don't move.
非常好
Very good.
服从我的规定...
It's important...
非常重要
that you obey my rules...
让你生死有别的规定
rules to make the difference between your life and your death.
我是葛特斯曼医生   有任何传染病吗？
I'm Dr. Gottesman. Any communicable diseases?
还没有
Not yet.
你说什么？
Excuse me?
你是伯克 对吧？
You're Burke, right?
你是AB型阴性的血 非常罕见
You have AB negative blood. That's very rare.
好, 请带他们到下一间房间去
Okay, take it into the next room, please.
快点！ 走
Come on. Move it.
你的识别号码是72688
Your identification number's 72688.
记住你的号码 72688
Memorize your number... 72688.
这是你的识别证  72688先生
This is your identification card, Mr. 72688.
你的新家是C层 C71号囚室
Your new home is C level, cell C-71.
下一个！
Next.
它死了(瞎了)   你说什么？
- It's dead. - Excuse me?
你在看的那只眼
The eye. You were looking at it.
瞎了  被刺瞎的
It's dead. Got stabbed in it.
刺你的眼？
Stabbed in the eye?
是的 我眼被刺
Yeah, I got stabbed in the eye.
4:27
好了, 你的毛巾及牙冠
Okay, you got your towel, you got your toothbrush.
每早6点10分炊事班开始
Meal shift starts every morning at 6:10.
洗衣服是中午开始不停  晚餐是下午6点30分
Lunch is noon straight up. Dinner is at 6:30 p. m.
你每天可以淋浴一次   检查自己的香港脚及身体
You can take a shower once a day, check yourself for fungus and body lice.
有问题吗？
Any questions?
你的识别号码是72689
Your identification number is 72689.
记住你的号码是72689
Memorize your number... 72689.
72689, 好  我叫伯克
72689. Right. My name is Burke.
你的识别证，72688先生
Here's your I.D. card, Mr. 72689.
你的新家在C层 C68囚室  下一个！
Your new home is C level. Cell C-68. Next.
好了, 你的毛巾及牙刷
Okay, you got your towel, you got your toothbrush.
滚吧 老兄
来啊！ 老兄
你在这里干什么？  你以为你在看什么？
What are you doing here? And what do you think you're looking at?
我是新来的
I'm new here.
我不管你是谁  你以为你能睡在这？
I don't care what you are. You think you can sleep here?
房地产  得花五百元
Real estate. Cost you $500.
我没有钱
Don't have any money.
你没有钱  那没有关系
You don't have any money? Well, that's okay.
你可以扮0号  你说什么？
- You can punk. - Excuse me?
你可以四肢着地趴下
You can get down on your hands and knees...
那你就算付了  就像其他的菜鸟
and you pay, just like any other cherry.
我不认为如此
I don't think so.
你不认为如此
You don't think so?
可能
Possibly...
你也许想重新考虑
you might wanna reconsider.
我不付钱 我不搞同性恋
I don't pay, I don't punk.
好了 别激动
Okay, okay. Take it easy.
我只是开你玩笑 你无需火大
I was jerking you around. Don't have a hair ball about it.
听我说 你要睡上铺？ 你睡    下铺还不错的
- You want the top bunk, take it. - The bottom would be nice.
没错，是你的了  谢谢
- Better yet. You got it. - Thanks.
72689, 记得吗？
72689, remember?
我记得  你不会想吃那个的
Yeah, yeah, I remember. Don't eat that.
我的食物有什么不对劲了？
What's wrong with my food?
黑鬼
Hey, nigger.
你在说我闲话？
Are you talking about me, ese?
普瑞兹, 我们现在不管闲事了
We keep to ourselves now.
我们不管你们的人的事
- We don't give a shit about you people. - Oh, yeah?
听我说...  是我的事
- Hey, listen. - Hey, it's on me!
让他走  叫他去死
- Let him go. Let him go. - It's cool, ese.
我杀了你！
You're dead, ese!
你死定了  你死定了！
You're fucking dead, ese!
死定了！
You're dead!
放开我
Let me go, homes.
我待会再跟你说
I'll talk to you later.
贺金斯
Hawkins.
我知道...永远都是黑鬼的错
I know... always the nigger's fault.
你不会支撑太久的
You're not gonna last too long.
那是威胁吗？
Is that a threat?
不是
No.
那是保证
That's a promise.
它从来没发生过
It never happened!
继续吃晚餐
Back to dinner!
你是鼠辈  死定了！
You're a rata, ese. Fucking dead.
扮0号的
杰克！ 兄弟, 到这边来
你是怎么回事？
What's the matter with you?
看不出这是黑人的座位
Can't you see this is a black table?
和你自己的同类待在一起  现在谁都别信任
Stick with your own kind. Trust no one.
那你呢？
What about you?
我怎样？你不知道我是谁？
What about me? You don't know who I am.
你什么都不知道
You don't know anything.
菜鸟
Hey, fish.
你为何不跟我们一起坐？ 菜鸟
Why don't you sit with us, fish?
坐下，聪明的孩子
Sit down, bright boy.
你是为何进来的？   我是个坏孩子
- So what are you in for? - I was a bad boy.
你呢？
And you?
我和这位皮屈犯了大案子，
Me and Keel here, we got the big bitch.
常客
Habitual.
看到这个了吗？
See these?
那些是他杀掉的人名
Those are the people he's killed.
非常的特别
That's very special.
把他们关起来了， 杰克
Lock 'em up, Dick.
开始算人
Begin count.
2--C层, 69人
Tier 2-C, 69.
2--C层, 68人
Tier 2-C, 68.
李子酒
Pruno.
我们自己酿的
Make it ourselves.
对苦恼你的那些东西有益
It's good for what ails you.
看到你为那老黑鬼贺金斯解围
I saw you helping out that nigger Hawkins.
不好  那很不好
Not good. It's bad mojo.
多数时候你甚至不能信任同类  懂我的意思吗？
Most of the time, you can't even trust your own kind in this place.
卡耐夫基
Hey, Konefke.
你在这多久了？
How long have you been here?
也许...六年了
Maybe six years.
我听说有许多人在垂死之中
I hear a lot of guys are dying.
卡耐夫基Konefke?
也许
Yeah, maybe.
但我看的不再那么清楚了
But I don't see so well no more.
我就像你听说的那些猴子之一
Like one of those monkeys you hear about.
非礼勿听， 非礼勿视
Hear no evil, see no evil.
看看你在那里
我在那里并没什么不妥
路易斯
Hi, Louis.
漂亮的装扮
That's a nice outfit.
谢谢
Thank you.
你想让我被杀？
Are you trying to get me killed?
你应该是我太太而不是公主
You're supposed to be my wife, not a princess.
我没注意到
I didn't realize.
下次注意点
Pay attention next time.
我查过这里的连续杀人案犯人了
I ran your M.O. check on serial killers here.
没有什么吻合的  我查过所有的死亡证明
Nothing matches up. I checked all the death certificates.
所有受害人都死于后脑受到重击
All the victims died of puncture wounds to the back of the skull.
也许不是什么  但我在想也许是帮派
Maybe it's a serial killer, but I'm thinking maybe it's gangs...
像是开香堂的杀人仪式
or, like, ritual killings.
让我们把注意力放在受害人身上
Let's concentrate on the big tips.
好，最后一个是艾文巴瑞特
Last one was Alvin Barrett.
他的室友 我会跟他谈
His cell mate, I'll talk to him.
你做的很好
You did good.
谢谢
Thanks.
我需要你绐我弄些钱来
I need you to give me some money.
我要办公室今天下午汇款进你狱中的帐户
I'll have the office credit your prison account this afternoon.
那不够好，我需要现金来买东西
That's no good. I need real cash to get anything done here.
受刑人不允许有现金的
Inmates aren't allowed to have cash.
你设法把钱带给我 就这么简单
You'll find a way to bring me the money easy.
路易斯, 我不知我是否能那么做
I don't know if I can do that.
我们在谈的是我的命
This is my life we're talking about.
我会把钱弄给你
I'll get you the money.
告诉孩子, 爹地爱他们
Tell the kids Daddy loves them.
我告诉你... 我不准
I'm telling you, I won't condone it.
金恩先生 若你不批准那些钱  我会自己给他
If you won't authorize the money, I'll give it to him myself.
别跟我耍招数 贝克特小姐
Don't play games with me, Miss Beckett.
你在这案子里只是连络人  如此而己！ 而且...
You are a liaison on this case and nothing more.
别激动
Take it easy.
别让他惹你生气
Don't let him get to you.
你另外一位可爱的好友？
Another one of your lovely peers?
海伦
Hi, Helen.
谢谢, 萝莎瑞达 我来
Thank you, Rosarita. I'll do it.
我多年前就不再问汤姆调查的事
I stopped asking Tom about these investigations years ago.
反正都是那么的脏
It's all so sordid anyway.
政治让你有兴趣吗？  不会！ 不再会了
- I thought politics interested you. - No, not anymore.
从我出院之后 事情有了新展望
Since I got out of the hospital, things have taken on a new perspective.
扮0号的！
还记得我吗？
Remember me?
尿桶
我要你见见我的老乡  布鲁斯
I want you to meet my homey. Bruce!
他喜欢打扁白种垃圾， 像你那样
He likes to kick the shit out of white trash like you, boy.
尿桶
你要怎么办？
So what you gonna do? Huh?
来啊！
你那些书哪来的？
Where'd you get all those books?
我太太，我们喜欢看书
My wife. We like to read a lot.
狗屎 我唯一看的是色情杂志
Shit. The only thing I read is girly magazine letters.
拿回去
Get back.
等一下，听听这一封
Listen to this one.
亲爱的先生
"Dear Sirs.
我从未想到这会发生在我身上  我上夜班
I never thought this would happen to me, but I was working the late shift...
大奶子欧巴桑来找我
when this big-titted mama comes up to me. "
这种事发生过吗？
You think any of this stuff ever really happens?
我不知道  从未发生在我身上
- Don't know. - Never happened to me.
贺金斯 你认识他吗？
Hawkins... you know him?
谢了
Thanks.
哈罗, 各位, 想念我吗？
Hello, guys. You miss me?
是独行侠
It's the Lone Ranger.
你好, 银子，什么事？ 奇莫沙比
Hi-ho, Silver. What's up, Kimosabe?
我的朋友就在这里面跳华尔滋
The man just waltzes right on in here...
并拜访快乐的老黑人
visits with the happy, old negros.
你是灰狼，伯克 你知道吗？
You're Lobo, Burke. You know that.
我是灰狼？
- I'm Lobo? - Yep.
你知道狼如何守护它的地盘  它在东西上面拉尿(惹火别人)
You know how wolves stake out their territory pissing on things?
我想你把这一带每样东西都惹火
I figure you pissed on just about everything around here.
你什么都知道 是吧？  我在这很久了
- You know everything, right? - Been here a long time.
你为何进来的？
What are you in for?
谋杀
Murder.
让我猜 你是...
Let me guess.
你是无辜的，对吧？
You're innocent, right?
不是
我捏死那个王八蛋是没错
I choked the son of a bitch just as sure as I'm sitting here.
我坐在这里己经超过十年了
Been here over ten years. That's a long time...
以卷香烟数蟑螂来说那是段长时间
to be rolling smokes and counting cockroaches.
那是什么
What's that?
在给气枪做子弹
Making shot for zip guns.
骇人的时代  人们从头上被打
Scary times. People getting spiked in the head and shit.
必须学会如何保护自己
Gotta learn to defend yourself...
那样你才不会化为尘土  我听过那说法
- So you don't get dusted. - I heard that, man.
你也许认为我欠你一份情  因为那天你所做的事
You probably figure I owe you something 'cause of what you did the other day.
巴瑞特，谁杀了他？他是我的朋友
Barrett... who killed him? He was my friend.
让我告诉你一件事 孩子  我根本就不认识你
Let me tell you something. I don't owe you jack shit.
你想知道你朋友发生了什么事？ 去见教士
You wanna know what happened to your friend? See the Priest.
教士？
The Priest?
我只说这些
That's all I'm saying.
我跟你说 老兄  你愈往下走就愈臭
I'm telling you, the lower you go, the funkier it gets in this place.
我们要去的地方连警卫都不会来
Down where we're going, the guards won't even come down here.
我要介绍你认识的人
This guy I'm gonna introduce you to...
教士  真他妈的 有部份是蛇
Priest, man. He's part fucking snake.
我知道你以为我盖你，但我不是
I know you think I'm shitting you, but I'm not.
当你看到他眼时， 别看得太久
Wait till you see his eyes. Don't look at 'em too long.
它令我起鸡母皮
It gives me the fucking creeps.
我跟你说 在这下面你得保自己  我亳不夸张的告诉你  那不是在高谈阔论
You gotta cover your ass down here, and I mean that literally.
你会发疯的，兄弟
It's gonna blow your mind, man.
对此事你要眼见为凭
You gotta see this.
什么？
What?
你在说些什么？
What are you talking about?
听着，那不是我们谈的交易  教士
- Look, that's not the deal we made. - Priest...
听着！听着！
Listen! Look.
我现在就要我的东西
I want my stuff now.
如同我以前所说过的
Like I started saying before...
教士 这是伯克
Priest, this is Burke.
Yeah.
我听说你爱打抱不平
I heard you went airborne on Perez.
想要位小姐吗？
You want a lady?
不想
No.
他认为我高攀不上 教士
He thinks he's too good for me.
我的小姐有什么不好？
What's wrong with my ladies?
没什么不好
Nothing.
我只是需要一些协助
I just need some help.
我帮许多人
I help lots of people.
我给洁西贺尔蒙药片
I get Jersey hormone pills.
你是需要那种帮助吗？
Is that the kind of help you want?
艾文贝瑞特， 谁杀了他？
Alvin Barrett... who killed him?
有人在他的头上打了一个洞
Someone punched a hole in his head.
为什么？
Why?
我无法就这样告诉你这些事
I can't just tell you these things.
我绐你一点点 你尝尝看
I give you a little, you taste it.
事情是这样办的
That's how things work.
你可以和拜尔森谈谈  贝瑞特以前的室友
You could talk to Myerson, Barrett's former cell mate.
他现在在单独囚室里
He's in solitary now...
但他在医务所工作，夜班
but he works in the infirmary, night shift.
若你有钱他就能绐你开处方
He can fill prescriptions if you got the money.
确信不想验验我的货色？
Sure you don't wanna sample my goods?
我看改天吧
I'll take a rain check.
又有一个了
Got another one.
他不会回家吃晚饭了
He won't be home for dinner.
这是什么？ 他妈的医药废弃物
- What is this? - Goddamn medical waste.
医药废弃物
Medical waste.
你是拜尔森？  你要什么？
- You Myerson? - What do you want?
我需要一些药
I need some medicine.
我可以弄到处方的药品 吗啡  你需要什么？
I got prescription drugs... morphine and uppers. What do you need?
我听说你是贝瑞特的室友  他是个好孩子？
I hear you were Barrett's cell mate. He was a good kid, huh?
他现在己经死了
- He's dead now. - Yeah.
毒品, 坏消息
On drugs. Bad news.
门都没有, 兄弟
No way.
他菜的跟什么鸟一样 他什么都没做过
He was as green as grass. He never did nothing.
抢一家便利商店而已
Convenience store robbery, and that's it.
也许他加入了帮派？
Maybe he was in a gang then.
我说了他是干净的  你那么好奇干什么
I said he was clean. What are you so curious about?
他是我的朋友，头上挨了一下
He was my friend who got spiked in the head.
也许你知道是谁干的
Maybe you know who did it.
我不会再说任何话  你会的
- I'm not saying another word. - Yes, you are.
你去死！
Hey, fuck you!
这是什么？
What is this?
是苏打水
It's soda pop.
你得喝了它
You're gonna drink this.
老兄，不要, 拜托  我什么都没做
Please, man, don't! I didn't do nothing! Christ!
我若说话他们会杀了我   一个警卫让他进来的 不是我
Look, they'll kill me if I talk. A guard let 'em in, not me.
锁门！ 还有五分钟，动作快
Lockup, five minutes. Move it!
我会再和你谈
I'll talk to you.
哈罗  是我伯克
- Hello? - It's Burke.
我查出了点头绪
I've got something.
稍候一下
Hang on a second.
好, 我预备好了
Okay, I'm ready.
贝瑞特的室友害怕了
Barrett's cell mate is scared.
不论那里在搞些什么， 警卫有份
Whatever's going on, the guards are involved.
我需要看受害人的档案
I need to see the victims'files.
档案尚未输入电脑中
The files haven't been transferred to computer yet.
哈瑞森的档案全都还在狱中
Harrison's files are all still at the prison.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
现在？
Right now?
吃晚餐
Eating dinner.
伯克？
Burke?
还有别的事吗？
Is there anything else?
我会保持连络
I'll be in touch.
聊的还愉快吗？
Have a nice little chat?
我要去记录室的钥匙
I need the key to the records room.
那可以安排
That can be arranged.
什么事？
- Hey! - What?
你那里是什么？ 贺金斯
What do you got here?
绐服务台的很多衬衫
A load of shirts for the reception desk.
好, 你抓到我了
Okay, you got me.
拿一些李子酒给在单独囚室的人
I was taking some pruno over to the guys in storage.
你知道我得拿走它， 贺金斯
Now, you know I'm gonna have to take that.
当然
Sure.
没关系, 拿去尝吧
You ever actually taste that stuff?
我不认为如此  没那么差
- I don't think so. - All right.
也许  我尝尝看
Well, maybe. Let me try some.
老兄
Oh, man!
你得先习惯它，
Well, you're gonna have to develop a taste for it.
不要猛灌！
You just can't go wading into the shit, you know.
(巴瑞恃SLB型RH阳性)
SL.RHSL.RH
新到的
New arrival.
到底有何关连？
那是什么？ 什么是什么？
- What was that? - What was what?
我一定是疯了
I must be going crazy.
不会的
这地方有很多老鬼阴魂不散
Lot of old ghosts hanging around this place.
我们出去吧
Let's get out of here.
只有谋杀受害人才有SL的记号
Only the murder victims have the "SL" notation.
受害人都是新来的  没有吸毒 没有入帮派
The victims are brand-new... no drugs, no gangs.
不同的年龄及种族
All different ages and race.
我能查主体系统
I can check with the mainframe system.
也许SL是部门的缩写
Maybe "SL" is some sort of departmental abbreviation.
我有个人能介绍给你
I've got the guy for you.
我以前与他共事过 是真正的职业高手
I've worked with him before. He's a real pro.
他会为你代工
He'll do the hacking for you.
而且别跟金恩提到此事 好吗？
And don't tell Keane about this, okay?
你知道这是非法的 对吧？
You know this is illegal, don't you?
算是非法的  你介意吗？
Sort of illegal. Do you mind?
你开玩笑吗？我喜欢！
Are you kidding? I love it.
知道吗？ 我喜欢把自己想成叛徒
See, I like to think of myself as a renegade.
知道吗？ 像是个牛仔
You know, like a cowboy.
我是个电脑牛仔  那就是我
Yeah, I'm a computer cowboy. That's what I am.
如何？  如何什么？ 它正在查
- Well? - Well, what? It's checking.
SL可能代表实际上的任何东西
"SL" can stand for virtually anything...
或什么都不是
or nothing at all.
如何？ 你有男友了吗？
So, you got a boyfriend or something?
电脑查询以SL起点的连结名词
The computer looks for combinations of words beginning with "SL."
然后再看档案中是否有那种名字
Then it sees if there are any files in the system named that.
狗屎 我看不到“星际迷航”了
Shit. I'm missing Star Trek.
你想看“星际迷航”吗？
You wanna watch Star Trek?
不想
No.
好  所以...
All right. So...
我们这里有些东西了
We got something here.
现在我们看那最经常输入的档案通常来自何处
Now we see where the files are most commonly accessed from.
中奖了！  就是它！ 那就是那份档案
- Bingo! - That's it. That's the file.
狗屎！ 我们需要密码
Shit! We need the password.
没关系, 那是个开始
That's okay. It's a start.
绐我一两天
Give me a day or two...
我能找出 自那输入的终端机位置
and I can locate any terminals it's been accessed from.
你去查出来是谁的档案
You'll find out whose file it was.
好极了  我送你回家  你父母会杀了我
Great. I'll take you home. Your parents'll kill me.
谁需要父母呢？ 我俩都是成人了，
Who needs parents? We're both adults.
不是吗？
Aren't we?
不，我是成人
I'm an adult...
而你是个孩子
and you're a kid.
而你的贺尔蒙在加班
Your hormones are working overtime.
来, 我送你回家
Come on. I'll take you home.
我宁愿不告诉金恩关于我用电脑所做的事
I'd rather not tell Keane about what I'm doing with the computers.
伯克似乎认为在没有他的干扰下我们能进行的快得多
Burke thinks we can get it done a lot quicker without his interference.
我在想伯克刑警是否干扰了你的工作习惯
I wonder if Detective Burke isn't interfering with your work habits.
我们有程序是有理由的
We have procedures for a reason.
我知道我在干什么 汤姆
I know what I'm doing.
我希望你知道
I hope you do.
我答应你父亲我会照顾你
I promised your father I'd take care of you.
别担心
Don't worry.
该死的！耽搁你够久了
Damn it! It took you long enough.
你现在要谈了吗？
You want to talk now?
听着！ 我发现了一些事   有关他们对贝瑞特做了什么事
Look, I found out some things... about what they did to Barrett.
他不该那样被他们对待
He didn't deserve what they did to him.
听着 我们以前把存量高的毒品走私到外面去
We used to smuggle out some drugs from overstock.
我昨晚在外科
Well, I was in surgery last night...
狗屎 葛特斯曼
Shit. That's...
若他发现钥匙不见了我就死定了
If he finds his keys missing, I'm a dead man.
别紧张
Relax.
别担心
Don't worry.
我需要保护
I need protection.
因为昨天又有人被打了  这是严重的...狗屎
Another guy got spiked last night, and this is serious shit!
安静
Quiet.
我得把这串钥匙还给教士
I've got to get this key back to Priest.
保护
Protection.
我需要保护
I need protection.
小白脸
Lady-killer.
我想你会想知道
Just thought you'd like to know...
今晚会有人来拜访你
I think somebody's gonna pay you a visit tonight.
关于睡觉我会再想一次
I'd think twice about sleeping.
谢了
Thanks.
我只是不愿看到一个好人浪费了
I just hate to see a good man go to waste.
我终于想出密码了
I finally figured out the password.
我让电脑逐个排列破解好几个小时
I've had the computer running word variations for hours.
当然你知道 它是我自己设计的特别程式
Of course, you know, it was a special program I devised myself.
知道吗？ 我在一本男性杂志上
You know, I was reading this article in a men's magazine...
看到一篇男孩子在青少年中后期  有关他们的男子气概
about the virility of men in their middle to late teens...
去做就对了，提斯坦
- Right. - Just do it.
对, 我们进行吧
Right. Here we go.
马斐斯 希腊的睡神
Morpheus was the Greek god of sleep.
我在神话学上是怪胎
I'm a whiz at mythology.
你的罪犯有幽默感
Criminals have a sense of humor.
是的！ 我们进去了
Yes! We're in.
你在开我玩笑
You're kidding me?
现在，你还需要什么别的吗？
No. Is there anything else you need?
印出来, 能印这档案吗？
Print it out. Can you make a copy of this file?
当然能  谢谢
- Sure I can. - Great.
它在干什么？
What the hell is it doing?
有人由另外一边在毁灭它
Someone is destroying it from the other end.
阻止它！  我不能
- Well, stop it. - I can't.
只能希望是先下指令印表的
We just have to hope it started the print copy first.
这档案是由那输入的？
Where's this file accessed from?
医务所是一个   我还在查其他的缩写
The infirmary, for one. I checked up on the other abbreviation.
HLE是种连续打字的密码系统
"H-L-E" is a coding system for a tissue type.
我还在查另一部份的输入
I'm still checking on that other point of access.
绝对是一个在监狱外的人
It's definitely someone outside the prison.
好了，那是我们的关键人物
That's our key player.
这是我呼叫器号码  一查出来就打给我 好吗？
This is my beeper number. Call me as soon as you find it out.
提斯戴尔，你真是神乎其技
Tisdale, you are a stud.
这“睡眠"档案的内容
All the Sleep file contained was a list of prisoner I.D. numbers...
是犯人的识别号码及他们的血型
strung together along with the prisoners' blood types.
在那名单上的每个人都被杀了
Every person who was on that list has been killed.
那是份死亡黑名单  完全正确
- It's a hit list. - Exactly.
每位受害人在遇害的前一星期
Each victim had a physical days before they were killed.
都有身体检查 结果都是没毛病
Each one came up clean.
你知道没有...病，没吸毒  什么都没有
No diseases, no drug addiction, nothing.
我认为是个外面的人与警卫合作
I think someone from the outside is working with the guards.
金恩？
Keane.
金恩输入过那档案
Keane would have access to the files.
伯克
Burke.
还有别的事
There's something else.
你的号码在名单上的下一个
Your number's next on the list.
这里是怎么回事？
What's going on in here?
帮我！
Help me.
抓住他！ 帮我！
- Grab him. - Help me!
你在我的监狱里干什么
What are you doing in my prison?
你的嘴有问题了？
Is something wrong with your mouth?
你杀了卡耐失基
You killed Konefke.
我没有
I didn't do it.
我知道
I know.
把他脱光
Strip him.
When I know you
When I know you like I know
你有张大嘴吧 洁西
You got a big mouth, Jersey.
罗...
老兄,我没有说任何的姓名
I didn't say no names.
我没有说是你
I didn't say you.
是谁在这里？
Who's there?
怎么回事？ 你想干什么？
What's going on? What do you want?
我们想谈谈，和伯克一样
We wanna talk, just like Burke.
我没有和伯克谈，我什么也没说
I didn't talk to Burke. I didn't say nothing.
谁说我与伯克谈过了 ？ 那是胡扯
Who said I talked to Burke? This is bullshit.
那是什么？
What is that?
狗屎 老天
Shit. Oh, God.
等一下，你不能这么做
Hey, wait a minute. You can't do this.
你们得听听我这一边的说词  我什么都没说 有人在说谎
You gotta hear my side of it. Somebody's lying, man!
有人对我的事说谎
Somebody's fucking lying on me!
我要昏倒了，你不能这么做
You can't do this, man!
天啊！ 住手！ 且慢！
Oh, God. Just stop. Wait a minute.
等一秒钟！
Just wait one second! Oh, God.
天啊！ 你对伯克说了什么
What did you say to Burke?
谁说我谈过的？ 你怎么知道的？
Who said I talked? How did you find that out?
那是胡说 老兄
That's bullshit, man!
不要！ 不 我对天发誓我没有   住手！ 你在干什么？
I swear to God I didn't talk! Stop it! What are you doing?
你疯了吗？ 住手！
You're crazy, man! People will find out!
你要我怎么做？你要我怎么做？
What do you want me to do? What do you want me to do?
你要什么？ 你要我怎么做？
I'll give you anything! What do you want?
不！ 不！
你是个骗子！ 拜尔斯
You're a liar, Myerson.
不！求你！
Don't! Please!
求你不要！
不！ 救救我啊！救命！
这太莫名其妙了
This is ridiculous.
你想见你丈夫吗？
Do you wanna see your husband?
皮包
The purse.
找个女警卫来
Then bring in a female guard.
似乎没有一个有空
None seem to be available.
手臂平举
Up with the arms.
我不知道
I don't know.
抱歉 小姐
I'm sorry, missy...
但你得把衣服脱了
but you're gonna have to remove your clothes.
你先生在等
Your husband is waiting.
洗干净, 穿衣服
Clean up and get dressed.
你那漂亮的娇小老婆想见你
Your pretty little wife wants to see you.
你有半个小时，伯克
You have a half hour, Burke.
在那里面玩爽一点 朋友
Have a good time there, buddy.
天啊！ 没关系的
- Oh, God. - It's okay.
是谁这样对你的？  警卫
- Who did this to you? - The guards.
他让两个人进入我的囚室
They let two prisoners into my cell.
其中一个拿了搓冰插
One of them had an ice pick.
至少我们知道是谁在插人了
At least we know who's been spiking people.
你呢？
What about you?
没什么
Nothing.
你看起来像鬼一样
You look like hell.
你也一样
So do you.
我查过葛特斯曼医生 以及...
I checked on Dr. Gottesman, and...
以及？
And?
他上的不是这里的医学院
He didn't get into med school here.
他到南美去念的
He went to South America.
南美？
South America?
还有...  还有？
- And, um... - And?
有几件...
There were a couple...
of, um...
医疗失当的控诉
malpractice suits.
你真美
You're so beautiful.
你们认为有大阴谋所以全呆住了
You guys are all spooked 'cause you think there's some big conspiracy.
你和我一样清楚是怎么回事
Priest, you know as well as I what's going on.
一位兄弟昨晚脑浆被挖了出来
Brother got his brains scrambled just last night.
像块肉般的把头骨打碎
Straight through the skull like a piece of meat.
下一个可能是我也可能是你
It could be me next, could be you.
所以那白种大超人要来救我们？
So big, white Superman's gonna save our asses?
是什么让你认为我们想要被救？
What makes you think we wanna be saved?
伯克需要我们的协助
Burke needs our help.
他需要分散注意力
He needs a distraction.
干的好, 贺金斯  谢谢教士
- Good work, Hawkins. - Thank the Priest.
狗屎   没错, 上了锁
- Shit! - Yeah, it's locked.
他们日夜把医药废弃物运出去
They cart this medical waste in and out of here day and night.
它们运去那？
- Where? - I don't know.
我不知道 有特别的取货  这太冒险
They got a special pickup for it. It's hazardous.
Oh, yeah?
让我们看看里面是什么  小心你的眼
Let's see what's inside. Watch your eye.
好笑，赶快吧
Funny. Hurry up.
拿著这个
Hold this.
是一颗人心
It's a human heart.
老天
Oh, God.
怎么回事？
What's going on?
一个新人被带进来
New dude being brought in.
这些都是为了一只菜鸟？
All this for a new fish?
这不是菜鸟  这是大哥大
Man, this ain't no fish. This is the man.
沙人
好久不见！ 伯克
Long time no see, Burke.
想知道是什么在外面吗？伯克
Would you like to know what's out there, Burke?
想知道是什么在另外一面吗？
Would you like to know what's on the other side?
你知道这犯人最恨的是什么 ？ 伯克
You know what prisoners hate more than anything else, Burke?
犯人最恨警察
Prisoners hate cops more than anything else.
他妈的猪罗！
Fucking pigs!
这监狱里的每一个杀手
Every killer in this prison...
都会知道你是谁
is gonna know who you are.
而你不会知道它何时会来
And you're not gonna know when it's coming.
放他走
Let him go.
带个梦给我！伯克
Bring me a dream, Burke.
带个梦给我！
Bring me a dream.
警察！
谁要保护你？ 警察
你属于我！
Hey, you belong to me!
他是个警察  唯一的好警察 记得吗？
He's a cop! The only good cop...
白人！ 你死定了！
我会撕裂你的屁股
I'm gonna rip your eyes out!
会让我有些乐趣的
Get me some chitlins.
我要如何才能离开这里？
I gotta get outta here!
你己经死了！
Get me out of this pen!
猪罗！
You pig!
你给我们的是一大堆屎！贝瑞特不是你的朋友
That's a load of shit you were giving us. Barrett wasn't your friend.
我在试著阻止这里发生的事
I'm trying to stop what's going on here.
那难道没有区别吗？
Doesn't that make a difference?
在牢里警察糟过...
In the cage, man, a cop is worse than a...
婴儿强奸者
baby raper.
你为何还在这里？
Why are you still here?
你是个死人了
You're a dead man.
我需要你的帮忙
I need your help.
己经太迟了
It's too late.
贺金斯
贝克特小姐，我一直在找你
Miss Beckett, I've been looking for you.
你离我远一点！
You stay the hell away from me.
汤姆！打扰    阿曼达 我需要与你谈谈
Tom. Excuse me. I need to speak with you.
有什么不对了 ？ 紧急事件
- What's wrong? - It's urgent.
是关于金恩的
It's about Keane.
我们到房里去
Let's go inside.
现在, 你要告诉我发生何事吗
Now, you want to tell me what's going on?
我们必须把伯克由那弄出来
We have to get Burke out of there.
金恩一直都在此事的幕后
Keane has been in on this the entire time.
等一下, 这一定和此事有关
Wait. This has to do with it.
提斯,是我    阿曼达, 听我说
- Yeah, Tis, it's me. - Amanda, listen.
我试着另一个输入的地方  号码是5556799
I tried the other point of access. The number's 555-6799.
是逢格家
Vogler's house!
抱数， 阿曼达  我从未想要这样
I'm sorry, Amanda. I never wanted this.
海伦和我真的关心你
Helen and I really did care about you.
不！
若海伦知道了，会杀死她的
If Helen found out, it would kill her.
我们必须...
We have to...
把我们生命中不好的部份不公开
keep the bad parts of our lives private.
伯克的证据是那么富有想像
Burke proved so resourceful...
当其他人没有了结他时
that when the others didn't take care of him...
我把沙人移监到那去了
I had the Sandman transferred there.
为什么？
Why?
我那么做是为了救她的命
I did it to save her life.
海伦病了，她需要一付肝
Helen got sick. She needed a liver.
她必须要得到一个
She couldn't get one.
不论我有多少的钱
It didn't matter how much money I had.
名单太长了
The list was too long.
于是我找到这位医生
So I found a doctor.
葛特斯曼
他说他可以弄到一付
He said he could get one.
而一旦他开始了
Once he started...
他发现他出售生命可以赚很多钱
he found you could make a lot of money selling life.
我们是杀人犯
We're killing criminals.
垃圾
Garbage.
一阵子之后
And after a while...
你会不再认为他们是人类
you stop thinking of them as humans.
汤姆，你在这...
Oh, Tom, there you are.
怎么回事？
What's going on?
你为何不告诉她？ 汤姆
Why don't you tell her, Tom?
告诉她你如何为她杀人
Tell her how you murdered for her.
海伦
伯克  沙人要看你了
Hey, Burke, Sandman's coming to see ya.
你没胆子进这间囚室
You don't have the guts to come in this cell.
兄弟！ 发生了什么事？
What happened?
怎么回事？ 发生了什么事？ 他撂倒凯勒了
- What happened? - He got Keller!
发生了什么事？
我会逮到你的！
杀了他！
老天爷！ 关上这道门   抓住他！
Jesus Christ! Secure this door! Grab him!
带他和我们一起走 快点
Bring him too. Come on.
安静
金！ 去守住服务台
Gene, secure the infirmary.
看看我们这里有什么
Well, well, look who we have here.
瑞斯, 现在所有的混蛋全都在一间房里了
Great. Now we have all the assholes in one room.
你造成我们很大麻烦 伯克刑警
You've caused us a great deal of trouble, Detective Burke.
你这杂碎
You scum.
让我来做
Let me do it.
会很棘手！ 杀卧底的警员
It's gonna be messy if you kill an undercover officer.
动手啊！ 挂了他
Go ahead, dust him.
轰掉他的头
Blow his fucking head off!
别玩了, 我们快离开这！ 走
Come on! Stop playing around! Let's get the hell out of here!
你为何这么做？
Why did you do it?
我不知道
I don't know.
也许我年纪大了心肠软
Maybe I'm going soft in my old age.
就说我欠某人一些东西
Let's just say I owe somebody something.
我们离开这  穿过厨房
- Let's get out of here. - Let's go through the kitchen.
快！ 通往厨房的电梯
Quick! The elevator to the kitchen!
天啊！
Oh, God.
你及时赶到动手术 医生
You're just in time for surgery, Doc.
我们走
Let's do it.
慢慢来   谢了
- Easy. - Thanks.
现在会痛了，行吗？
It's going to hurt now, okay?
别问我
Yeah. Stop yacking at me.
没人了, 我们一阵子没有问题
It's secure. We're okay for a while.
小心
你能走吗？
Can you make it?
我想不能  他最好留在这里
- I don't think so. - He's better off here.
我必须到外面去
I have to get to the outside.
我会回来找你们的
I'll be back for you.
支撑住
Just hang on.
跟他一起走, 兄弟  确定他能到外面去
Go with him, man. Make sure he gets to the outside.
去啊！
Go on! Go on!
我知道你在里面 伯克
I know you're in here, Burke.
你知道为什么吗？
You know why?
因为我能闻到那个黑鬼
'Cause I can smell the nigger.
吻你的黑屁股再见吧
Kiss your black ass good-bye.
自己玩自己吧！ 杂种
Go fuck yourself, you pudgy bastard.
我知道你会需要我 兄弟
I knew you needed me, brother.
你和教士做了交易  那是保证实现的
You make a deal with the Priest, it's for keeps.
伯克
Burke.
贺金斯？
Hawkins.
他没事 你比他更需要我
It's okay. You need me more than he does.
跟我来
Follow me.
我们必须走小径  经由锅炉室
We have to take the catwalk through the boiler room.
那是唯一到院子里去的路
That's the only way to get out to the yard.
来啊！ 伯克！
Come on, Burke!
到爸爸这里来
Come to Papa!
教士
Priest.
我在上面！ 伯克
I'm up here, Burke!
假如你走 贺金斯就得死
If you leave, Hawkins dies!
来啊！
Come on!
你喜欢吗？ 伯克
You like that, Burke?
这是我喜爱的部份
This is the part I love.
他在那边！我们逮到他了！
快！ 快！ 快！
Move, move, move!
踢他！
醒醒！ 伯克
Wakey, wakey, Burke.
流血的时候到了
Time to bleed.
来啊！
Come on!
加油！ ...
欢迎光临地狱
Welcome to hell!
伯克！
沙人...
你杀不了我的！伯克
Can't kill me, Burke.
我是沙人
I'm the Sandman.
让他过  让他走, 兄弟
- Let the man through. - Let him go, man.
让开！ 让他出去！
- He just dusted the Sandman. - Open up, man. Let him out.
让他过
Let him go by.
他办到了, 兄弟
You did it, man.
他真的办到了，他把他挂了
You really did it. You dusted him.
让开！ 他刚把沙人绐踢倒
Open up, man. Open up. He just kicked up the Sandman.
退后
Back up, vatos.
后面的让条路出来
Clear it out back there.
你办到了，老乡
You got it, homes.
伯克
轻点
Easy.
这是贺金斯 他救了我的命
This is Hawkins. He saved my life.
我不得不救，伯克
I had to, Burke.
我夺取了一条性命 我归还一条
I took a life. I gave one back.
也许现在我扯平了
Maybe now I'm even.
自己小心, 72689
Just watch your ass, 72689.
下一次我不会在那里了
I won't be there the next time.
剧 终